http://www.anders.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Home
Display Solutions
Colour DisplaysMonochrome DisplaysCircular DisplaysLetterbox DisplaysEmbedded DisplaysProducts
LED Solutions
Embedded Solutions
Industrial IoT Gateway PCsSingle Board ComputersComputer On ModulesEmbedded DisplaysProducts
Design Services
Optical performance
Display CoverlensFilms and FiltersOptical BondingBacklight customisationDisplay Technology
Antimicrobial TouchscreensTouch and firmwareHardware DesignSoftware developmentMechanical Integration
Markets
Medical DevicesHome AppliancesIndustrial ControlUtility & Smart MeteringMarine & AutomotiveRetail & Signage
News & Tech
Blog and EventsCase StudiesWhite PapersStoriesGlossary
Why Anders?
Project JourneyCertificationsMeet the Team
Contact
Privacy Policy
The Anders Electronics privacy policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.
We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. We may change this Policy from time to time so please check this page occasionally to ensure that you’re happy with any changes.
Who are we?
Anders Electronics plc a company registered in England and Wales with company registration number is 00507451 and registered office at Acre House, 11-15 William Road, London NW1 3ER and main trading address and data controller is at Kings Studios, 43-45 Kings Terrace, London NW1 0JR are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
How do we collect information from you?
We collect information from you when you use our website about products or services or sign up for our regular email communications. In addition, we collect information when you place an order by telephone or email.
What type of information do we collect from you?
The personal information we collect might include your name, address, email address and phone numbers.We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, credit reference agencies) and may receive information about you from them.In addition, our company uses third parties to provide information about visitors to our websites, pages accessed and when. When you visit our websites, we will record your IP address to provide us with information about your visit. This information may identify the organisation to whom the IP address is registered but not individuals.
How is your information used?
To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered between you and usTo provide you with information, products and services that you request from usTo provide you with relevant information about goods and services we offerTo notify you about changes to our servicesTo seek your views or comments on the service we provideAs part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secureAt any time, you can update your preferences by clicking the link in any emails you receive from us, or send an email to info@andersdx.com.
Who has access to your information?
We will not sell or rent your information to third parties and we will only share your information with third parties when we need to complete a transaction – e.g. when arranging for a courier company to deliver goods that you have ordered.
Where we store your personal data
The data that we collect from you will be stored on our secure servers but may be required to be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA") for contractual obligations, such as being passed to our manufacturing partners. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will do our best to protect your personal data, but cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. We will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.If you purchase a product from us, your card information is not held by us, it is collected by our third-party payment processors, who specialise in the secure online capture and processing of credit/debit card transactions.
Cookies
Like many other websites, the Anders website uses cookies. 'Cookies' are small pieces of information sent by an organisation to your computer and stored on your hard drive to allow that website to recognise you when you visit. They collect statistical data about your browsing actions and patterns and do not identify you as an individual. For more information on our cookie policy, follow this link.
Your rights
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes and can exercise your right by unsubscribing from communications we send you or contacting us by e-mail at info@andersdx.comOur site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. You can access data we hold about you at any time by emailing us at info@andersdx.com
loading...
